const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ἰχθύς',
    answers: ['vis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἀνάστασις',
    answers: ['verrijzenis', 'opstanding'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἀποκάλυψις',
    answers: ['openbaring'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἄφεσις',
    answers: ['vergeving'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'γνῶσις',
    answers: ['kennis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δύναμις',
    answers: ['kracht'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'θλῖψις',
    answers: ['verdrukking', 'moeilijke situatie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'κρίσις',
    answers: ['oordeel'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'παράδοσις',
    answers: ['traditie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πίστις',
    answers: ['geloof'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πόλις',
    answers: ['stad'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'συνείδησις',
    answers: ['geweten'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'βασιλεύς',
    answers: ['koning'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'γραμματεύς',
    answers: ['schriftgeleerde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἱερεύς',
    answers: ['priester'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἀρχιερεύς',
    answers: ['hogepriester'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson31Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson31-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 31 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson31Vocabulary
